Preliminary Inventory of the Committee on the Present Danger records
Hoover Institution Archives
- Is the Reagan Defense Program Adequate Legislative File. Contains the 42-page brochure of 17 March 1982 and related materials, including the 9 May 1980 brochure Countering the Soviet Threat-U.S. Defense Strategy in the 1980's, against which Reagan's build-up is (Folder 87)
- Loose material (Folder 87)
- Charles Kupperman materials, mainly about his dissertation (Folder 87)
- SALT Dissertation (Folder 87)
- Carter (Folder 88)
- Loose material (Folder 88)
- Charles Kupperman speeches, notes, articles, and a few letters (Folder 88)
- Charles Kupperman Resume (Folder 88)
- Dole (?) RJ (R) Kansas (Folder 88)
- U.S. Senators materials, including Cochran, Goldwater, and others. (Folder 88)
- U.S. Senators materials (Folder 89)
- U.S, Senator's Statements in Support of or in opposition to SALT II, collected by Kupperman (2 folders) (Folder 89)
- Kupperman: CPD Meetings with agenda for 5 October 1981 (Folder 89)
- Loose material, including various copies of "Where We Stand on Arms Control," private draft, 6 December 1985 (one copy in an enveloppe contains remarks by Acheson) (Folder 89)
- File Cabinets Master Index, probably compiled in 1990 (Folder 89)
- CPD START Paper. Contains drafts copies of Where We Stand on START and Arms Control, and other materials, including David Trachtenberg, Why Compliance Matters 1985 (Folder 90)
- CPD START Paper. Contains materials by David Trachtenberg on START 1988-1991. (Folder 90)
- "Where We Stand on Arms Control," draft annotated copies of 16 January 1986. Includes a letter of comments by Douglas Dillon suggesting less strident rhetoric as well as comments by Van Cleave and Rowny (Folder 91)
- "Where We Stand on Arms Control," draft annotated copies of May 1986. Includes a letter to Tyroler from Mark Schneider, on behalf of Iklé, thanking for the manuscript and arguing about mobile missiles, 23 May 1986 (Folder 92)
- "Where We Stand on Arms Control," draft annotated copies and final version of 15 July 1986. (Folder 93)
- Where We Stand on Arms Control press conference, 16 July 1986. Inlcudes media reactions to the publication of the report (Folder 93)
- CPD START Paper. Contains draft annotated copies of Where We Stand On START, 1983, a statement by Dr. William R. Graham before the Board of Directors, CPD, at the sixth annual meeting, 11 November 1982; ACDA Transition Final Report-Part 1-Policy and Issues; and advice by Nitze and Mike May on what the incoming Reagan administration (Folder 93)
- Where We Stand on Arms Control draft annotated copies, comments by Kampelman and others (Folder 94)
- Where We Stand on Arms Control draft annotated copies, first cut 6 January 1985; 29 October 1985; first cut 1 November 1985 (Folder 94)
- Democratic National Convention, 1980 (Folder 94)
- Carter campaign, 1980 (Folder 94)
- Carter, articles on campaign (Folder 95)
- John B Anderson, articles on campaign (Folder 95)
- Edward M. Kennedy (Folder 96)
- George Bush (Folder 97)
- Loose parts of Hearings on SALT II (1979) (Folder 97)
- SALT II, Intelligence Committee Hearings. Includes Prepared Statements of Paul Nitze for presentation before the select committee on Intelligence, 20, July 1979 and 30 July 1979 (Folder 97)
- SALT II, Senate Select Committee on Intelligence: Newspaper Coverage (Folder 97)
- SALT II, Senate Foreign Relations Committee Hearings, 9 July-2 August 1979 (4 folders) (Folder 98)
- SALT II, Senate Foreign Relations Committee Hearings, 6 September-1979 (Folder 98)
- SALT II, Senate Foreign Relations Committee Hearings, 6 September-25 September 1979 (Folder 99)
- Current News and Selected Statements, 1986-1990 (Folder 99)
- "Someone you know needs a helping hand, Combined Federal Campaign," Video tape, 1980 (Folder 100)
- Nitze articles, 1990-1991 (Folder 100)
- Loose material (Folder 100)
- SALT II-The objectives vs. The Results, CPD paper, speech by Paul Nitze before the CCFR, 5 December 1978 (Folder 100)
- Current SALT Negotiating Posture, Nitze papers on SALT, 20 November 1978, and copy of January 15, 1979 (Folder 100)
- Letter from Rostow to Nitze on his forecasting of future Soviet moves, 12 May 1980 (Folder 100)
- Letter from Rostow to Nitze on Middle East developments, 20 February 1980 (Folder 100)
- Other Nitze correspondence (Folder 100)
- The President's 1980 State of the Union Address, A Response by Paul H. Nitze, Feb 1980 (Folder 100)
- Vienna SALT II terms summary, June 25, 1979 (Folder 100)
- Nitze, Hill Letter (Folder 100)
- Nitze, public addresses and articles, 1974-1977 (Folder 100)
- Nitze, "Next Steps for SALT" (Folder 100)
- Nitze, Statement before Republican Platform Committee 8 July 1980 (Folder 100)
- Nitze, statements before committees of House or Senate, 1979-1980 (4 folders) (Folder 100)
- Nitze, statements by before committees of House or Senate, 1979-1980 (9 folders) (Folder 101)
- Nitze, statements and speeches before various audiences, 1979-1980 (24 folders) (Folder 103)
- Nitze, containing statements and speeches by, interviews of, and correspondence (16 folders) (Folder 103)
- Nitze, correspondence File (Folder 103)
- Loose material by Nitze (Folder 103)
- Nixon articles, 1977-1990 (Folder 103)
- Nofziger, Lyn (Folder 103)
- Perle, Richard (Folder 104)
- Perle (Folder 104)
- Loose brochures and booklets (Folder 104)
- Air Force Magazine "In Focus..." (Folder 104)
- SALT II, Armed Forces Journal (Folder 104)
- Loose articles, papers, and analysis on SALT II (Folder 105)
- SALT II articles (2 folders) (Folder 105)
- Kaiser, Robert G. (Folder 105)
- SALT II, Representative Jack Kemp (Folder 105)
- SALT II newspaper coverage, SALT II and NATO, and MX, negotiating techniques (8 folders) (Folder 106)
- Soviet PRC Negotiations. Contains articles on Soviet-Chinese relations, 1979-1989 (Folder 107)
- SALT: II, The Best We Can Do? Republican National Commttee (Folder 107)
- SALT II, Senators' Statements (2 folders) (Folder 107)
- SALT II, Senators' Statements (Folder 107)
- SALT, including Senators' Statements, newspaper coverage, Congressional Votes, and Senate Vote Count (5 folders) (Folder 108)
- CPD transparent slides series (Folder 108)
- CPD transparent slides series (Folder 109)
- An Evaluation of U.S. and Soviet strategic Capability through the mid-1980s: A Comparative Analysis" CPD press releases (Folder 109)
- Gene Rostow correspondence, 1978 (Folder 109)
- CPD Gene V. Rostow, 1977 (Folder 109)
- Rostow correspondence about his article "Is Peace Divisible?" 1981 (Folder 109)
- Loose material, mainly articles, by Rostow (Folder 109)
- Publications by Rostow (Folder 110)
- SALT II, Senate Armed Services Committee Am. Moorer/Wilson, 31 July 1979. Contains articles and speeches by Rowny (Folder 110)
- Rostow Committee, Supporting news items, and Congressional comments. Contains various documents, including on Citizens Committe for Peace with Freedom in Vietnam, Rostow, Tyroler, Nitze and years 1974-1976 (Folder 111)
- Rowny, Edward L. 1981-1983 (Folder 111)
- SALT II, Lt. Gen. Edw. L. Rowny (Ret.). Also contains articles and statements by Rowny and a few letters (Folder 112)
- Shultz, 1986 (Folder 112)
- Shultz, 1985 (Folder 113)
- Shultz, 1984 (Folder 113)
- SALT II newspaper coverage, Soviet activities (2 folders) (Folder 113)
- SALT II, Soviet activities (Folder 113)
- SALT, Soviet defenses v. cruise missiles (Folder 113)
- SALT II, Soviet statements (Folder 114)
- SALT II, the summit meeting (Folder 114)
- SALT II, television coverage "The Advocates" (Folder 114)
- SALT II, television coverage, various shows (5 folders) (Folder 114)
- Secretary of State articles, circa 1989-1991 (Folder 115)
- Secretary of Defense articles, circa 1989-1991 (Folder 115)
- National Security Advisor articles, circa 1989-1991 (Folder 115)
- Bush (Folder 116)
- Vice president (Folder 116)
- SALT II, Graphics including maps and cartoons (Folder 117)
- SALT II, Heritage Foundation briefing book (Folder 117)
- Bush Transition, 1988-Jan. 20, 1989 (Folder 117)
- SALT II, newspaper coverage, editorials/ columnists, 1979 (Folder 118)
- SALT II, newspaper coverage, editorials/ columnists, 1978 (Folder 118)
- SALT II, endorsements / negatives (Folder 118)
- SALT II, endorsements (Folder 118)
- SALT II, SALT sellers (Folder 118)
- SALT II, draft papers and statements (Folder 119)
- SALT III (Folder 119)
- FPA SALT Paper, November 1978 (Folder 119)
- SALT II, newspaper coverage, editorials/ columnists, 1979-1980 (Folder 119)
- SALT II, (11 folders) they correspond to items 11) to 16) of "Cabinet V (drawer B)" (Folder 120)
- SALT II, (6 folders) they correspond to items 3) to 6) of "Cabinet V (drawer B)" (Folder 121)
- SALT II, (3 folders) they correspond to items 1) to 3) of "Cabinet V (drawer B)" (Folder 122)
- Announcement of Negotiations U.S.'s strategic concept 26 January 1985 (Folder 122)
- Shultz-Gromyko Meeting 7 January 1985 (Folder 122)
- INF treaty preliminary analysis. Contains draft annotated copies of a CPD Statement, "Analysis of the Intermediate-range Nuclear Forces (INF) Treaty" November 1987-February 1988 (Folder 122)
- Executive committee articles (Folder 122)
- U.S.-Soviet Negotiations, 1985-1986 (19 folders) they correspond to items 36) to 38) of "Cabinet VI (drawer B)" (Folder 123)
- U.S.-Soviet Negotiations, 1986-1987, (12 folders) they correspond to items 7) to 18) of "Cabinet VI (drawer B)" (Folder 124)
- U.S.-Soviet negotiations and Senate ratification debates, 1987, they correspond to items 1) to 6) of "Cabinet VI (drawer B)" (Folder 125)
- U.S.-Soviet Negotiations and Senate ratification debates, 1987, they correspond to items 1) of "Cabinet VI (drawer B)" (Folder 126)
- SALT II, (7 folders) they correspond to items 7) to 12) of "Cabinet V (drawer D)" (Folder 127)
- SALT II verification, (4 folders) they correspond to item 13) of "Cabinet V (drawer D)" (Folder 128)
- Contains loose material, including issues of Global Affairs (Folder 129)
- Small ICBM-Midgetman (Folder 129)
- U.S. ICBM Vulnerability (Folder 129)
- Counterforce (Folder 129)
- Cruise missiles (ALCM, SLCM, GLCM) (Folder 130)
- B-1 (Folder 130)
- Loose material on U.S. nuclear weapons (Folder 131)
- Post series on B-2 (Folder 131)
- U.S. bombers (Folder 131)
- Bombers (Stealth) (Folder 132)
- Current News issues (Folder 132)
- Current News issues (Folder 133)
- Current News issues and other DoS documents (Folder 134)
- Documents from DoS on Nicaragua (Folder 135)
- Wienberger, Caspar W. (Folder 135)
- Weinberger, 1982 (Folder 136)
- Weinberger, 1984 (Folder 136)
- Weinberger, 1983 (Folder 137)
- Weinberger, 1988- (Folder 137)
- Weinberger, 1985 (Folder 137)
- Weinberger, 1986-1987 (Folder 138)
- Warnke (2 folders) (Folder 138)
- William Van Cleave (Folder 138)
- Vance (Folder 139)
- Stockman, David A. (Folder 139)
- [Stansfield] Turner (Folder 139)
- Shultz (Folder 139)
- Selected Readings from Soviet Military Thought (1963-1973), selected and compiled by Douglass and Hoeber, produced by System Planning Corporation, April 1980, 693 pages (Folder 140)
- Reagan, 1985 (Folder 140)
- Reagan, 1983 (Folder 141)
- Reagan, 1984 (Folder 142)
- Reagan, 1982 (Folder 143)
- Reagan, 1987 (Folder 144)
- Reagan, 1988 (Folder 144)
- Reagan (Folder 144)
- Reagan, January 1981 (Folder 145)
- Reagan, November 1980 (Folder 145)
- Reagan, December 1980 (Folder 145)
- Magazines, early 1980s (Folder 145)
- World Military Expenditures and Arms Transfers, 1986, 1988 (Folder 146)
- Budget, 1990-1991 (Folder 146)
- Defense budget, fiscal year 1990 (Folder 146)
- Defense budget, fiscal year 1991 (Folder 147)
- Dr. Fred Charles Iklé, Testimonies, 1988 (Folder 148)
- Defense budget, fiscal year 1989 (Folder 148)
- DoD budget, fiscal year 1988 (Folder 148)
- Congressional testimony, fiscal year 19881988 (Folder 149)
- DoD budget, fiscal year 19871987 (Folder 149)
- Congressional testimony, fiscal year 19871987 (Folder 149)
- DoD budget, fiscal year 19861986 (Folder 150)
- Loose issues of Current News and other documents (Folder 150)
- Loose issues of Current News and other documents (Folder 151)
- Soviet doctrine and strategy, 1983- (Folder 151)
- Soviet doctrine and strategy, 1976-1982 (Folder 151)
- NATO, 1990 (Folder 152)
- NATO, 1989 (Folder 152)
- NATO, 1984 (Folder 153)
- NATO, 1983 (Folder 153)
- NATO, 1982 (Folder 154)
- NATO, 1981 (Folder 154)
- NATO, Theater Nuclear Balance (Folder 155)
- Air Force documents on environmental impact analysis process (Folder 155)
- Air Force documents on environmental impact analysis process (Folder 156)
- The MX system and the environment (Folder 156)
- NATO, 1977-1979 (Folder 156)
- Peace Academy material on the U.S. Institute of Peace (Folder 156)
- PFIAB / IOB (Folder 157)
- State Department (Folder 157)
- Fact Sheet on Voice of America, Radio Free Europe/Radio Liberty, 14 July 1980 (Folder 157)
- Adelman (Folder 157)
- Allen, Richard V. (Folder 158)
- Baker, James III (Folder 158)
- Brown (Folder 159)
- Brzezinki (Folder 1519)
- Bush, George (Folder 160)
- Loose booklets (Folder 160)
- Loose booklets (Folder 161)
- "Has America Caught Up?" Contains material, including draft annotated copies, on the analysis produced by CPD in September of 1989, "Is America Catching up? The U.S.-Soviet Military Balance 1989" (Folder 161)
- Tenth Annual Meeting conference, 6 Nov 1986 (Folder 162)
- Tenth Annual Meeting program, lists, transcripts, 6-7 November 1986 (Folder 162)
- Ninth Annual Meeting conference, 7 Nov 1985 (Folder 162)
- Ninth Annual Meeting, 7-8 November 1985 (Folder 162)
- William R. Graham Dinner, Sulgrave Club, 21 Feb 1986 (Folder 162)
- Board Inagural Reception, 1985 (Folder 162)
- Eighth Annual Meeting conference, 8 Nov 1984 (Folder 162)
- Eighth Annual Meeting, 8-9 November 1984 (Folder 162)
- Seventh Annual Meeting conference, 10 Nov 1983 (Folder 162)
- Seventh Annual Meeting, 10-11 November 1983 (Folder 162)
- Sixth Annual Meeting, 11-12 November 1982 (Folder 162)
- Sixth Annual Meeting conference, 1982 (Folder 162)
- Inaugural Sulgrave dinner, hosted by the executive committee, 19 January 1981 (Folder 162)
- Fifth Annual Meeting, 12-13 November 1981 (Folder 163)
- Fifth Annual Meeting conference, 1981 (Folder 163)
- Fourth Annual Meeting conference, 6 Nov 1980 (Folder 163)
- Fourth Annual Meeting, 6-7 November 1980 (Folder 163)
- Third Annual Meeting, 1979 (Folder 163)
- Annual Meeting conference, 8 Nov 1979 (Folder 163)
- Second Annual Meeting, 8-9 November 1978 (Folder 163)
- Annual Meeting conference at Shoreham, Nov-78 (Folder 163)
- Annual Meeting transcripts, 1978 (Folder 164)
- First Annual Meeting, 10-11 November 1977 (Folder 164)
- Annual Meeting planning (Folder 165)
- Fifteenth Annual Meeting, 7-8 November 1991 (Folder 165)
- Fourteenth Annual Meeting, 8-9 November 1990 (Folder 165)
- Thirteenth Annual Meeting, 9-10 November 1989 (Folder 165)
- Twelfth Annual Meeting, 10-11 November 1988 (Folder 165)
- Eleventh Annual Meeting, 5-6 November 1987 (Folder 165)
- Annual Meeting transcripts, 1979 (Folder 166)
- Annual Meeting transcripts, 1977 (Folder 166)
- Trends in the U.S. / Soviet Military Balance: A Present Danger? Manuscript, rough draft for CPD Executive Committee, comment only, F.P. Hoeber, 26 Oct 1977 (Folder 166)
- Citizens Committe for Peace with Freedom in Vietnam materials (Folder 167)
- Correspondence mainly about membership between CPD (generally Tyroler or Rostow) and various people whose name begins with letter N, O, P, R. (6 folders) (Folder 168)
- Correpondence between CPD and Bernard T. Renzy (Folder 168)
- Correspondence between CPD and Ronald Reagan before and after his election, 1980 (Folder 168)
- Rostow Confirmation (Folder 168)
- SALT II poll questions nad results, conducted for CPD by George Fine Research, Inc. 23 February-3 March 1979 (Folder 168)
- Kelly, John B corresopondence (Folder 169)
- Is the Reagan Defense Program Adequate materials (Folder 169)
- "Has America Become Number Two?" Military Balance, 29 Jun 1982 (Folder 169)
- Poll by Penn and Schoen Associates, Apr-84 (Folder 170)
- "Has America Become Number Two?" (Folder 170)
- "Has America Become Number Two?" Proofs and copies (Folder 170)
- Alerting America original tables and figures (Folder 170)
- Defense and the Deficit, 8 Mar 1985 (Folder 171)
- "Can America Catch Up?" Nov-84 (Folder 171)
- Consultants and staff expenses, 1986 - (Folder 171)
- Federal Form 941 1980-1985 (Folder 171)
- Federal Form 990 1976-1985 (Folder 171)
- Courier Services, 1978-1985 (Folder 171)
- Receptionist (Folder 171)
- Valerie Corda (Folder 171)
- Suzanne M. Crow (Folder 171)
- CPD, EK, Caroline W. (Folder 171)
- Endres, Jocqulyn R. (Folder 171)
- Alison Frazier Games, Summer Intern, 22 Jun 1981 (Folder 171)
- Paul S. Green, financial material relative to the employment and a few jokes and songs about the CPD team (Folder 172)
- Hansen, Beatrice H. (Folder 172)
- Kavahagh, Agnes M. (Folder 172)
- CPD, Hupperman, Charles (Folder 172)
- Moon, William M. (Folder 172)
- Perreault, Barbara Ann, 6-Sep-88 (Folder 172)
- Roe, Deborah A. (Folder 172)
- Schrotz, Margaret C. (Folder 172)
- Sharfman, Sherry G. (Sarah) (Folder 172)
- Temporaries (Folder 172)
- Sherman, Sally (Folder 172)
- Triber, Elaine M. (Folder 172)
- CPD, Consultants. See also Staff 1976-1980 (Folder 172)
- CPD, Staff expenses. Also see consultants 1977-1985 (Folder 172)
- Merril Lynch CDs and T-bills, 1983-1989 (Folder 173)
- Merril Lynch Ready Assets Trust (Folder 173)
- Present Danger, Russian Intensions (Folder 174)
- Future Statement, The U.S, the Soviets, and East Asia (General Stilwell) (Folder 174)
- Future Statement, SALT Comprehensive (Folder 174)
- A proposal: East-west Trade and Technology transfer (Folder 174)
- Strategic Defense Initiative project for a future statement (Folder 174)
- Future Statement: Projection of Soviet power (Folder 174)
- Panama Canal (Folder 174)
- North-south east-west connection, Scott Thompson (Folder 174)
- East-west Trade and Technology transfer. Contains material regarding Bill Van Cleave's Technology Transfer and U.S. Security (Folder 174)
- Present Danger, Future Statements: NATO (Folder 174)
- Present Danger, Future Statements: Military Pay and Structure (Folder 174)
- CPD future statements materials (10 folders) (Folder 175)
- ACDA transition materials, Rostow statement for his confirmation hearings, and problems of personnel in ACDA materials (Folder 175)
- ACDA Rostow, 1982 (Folder 176)
- ACDA Adelman (Folder 176)
- Where we Stand on Arms Control, Spring, 1986 (Folder 176)
- Elmo Zumwalt correspondence (Folder 176)
- CPD Polls, August 1986 (Folder 177)
- The 1980 Crisis AND What We Should Do About It, 22 January 1980. Contains draft annotated copies of the booklet, a memorandum for Senator Kennedy dated 23 January 1980, and a Draft of Basic Foreign Policy Speech for Kennedy (Folder 177)
- The Fifth Year... and the New Administration brochure material, 11 Nov 1981 (Folder 177)
- Nitze Response to the President's 1980 State of the Union address, 6 February 1980 (Folder 178)
- Quick Fixes to U.S. Strategic Nuclear Forces, statement or manuscript, 14 Mar 1980 (Folder 178)
- The Fourth Year-What We Have Said 1976-1980 and... What Has Benn Said About Us brochure, 6 Nov 1980 (Folder 178)
- Countering the Soviet Threat-U.S. Defense Strategy in the 1980's brochure, 9 May 1980 (Folder 178)
- H, contains correspondence with people whose name begins with an H (Folder 179)
- I (Folder 179)
- J (Folder 179)
- K, including a very funny one called "KOOKS" (letters from crazy or angry people) (Folder 179)
- Present Danger: Closeup (Folder 180)
- Jim Courter, Member of Congress (Folder 180)
- Congress (Folder 180)
- D (Folder 180)
- E (Folder 180)
- Embassies (Folder 180)
- F (Folder 180)
- G (Folder 180)
- XYZ (Folder 181)
- A (Folder 181)
- B (Folder 181)
- Yacobson, Sergius (Folder 182)
- Zumwalt, Elmo R. Jr. (Folder 182)
- Luce, Clare Both (Folder 182)
- T (Folder 182)
- W (Folder 182)
- S (Folder 183)
- Teller, Dr Edward (Folder 183)
- U (Folder 183)
- W (Folder 183)
- Walker, Charls E. (Folder 183)
- Rostow, Eugene V., 1983 (Folder 184)
- Ridgway, General M. B. (Folder 184)
- Smith, Loyd H. (Folder 184)
- T (Folder 184)
- S (Folder 185)
- R (Folder 185)
- Q (Folder 185)
- Mailings, Membership (Folder 186)
- N (Folder 186)
- O (Folder 186)
- P (Folder 186)
- Packard, David (Folder 186)
- Press (Folder 186)
- "Is A Nuclear Freeze In The Interest Of U.S. Security?", issued by CPD, 1983 (Folder 187)
- Problems with "The Nuclear Freeze," contains material related to this brochure (Folder 187)
- Soviet Military production under Gorbachev 1985-1989 (Folder 187)
- Military Balance, contains material for a draft point paper on military balance and arms control issues as well as other files on the same subject (Folder 187)
- Lee, contains material, including a few comments, related to a 32 pages report by CPD, on Soviet Defense Expenditures, press release on May 16, 1989 (authored by Bill Lee, working for the DIA) (Folder 188)
- Soviet Military Spending (Folder 188)
- Loose material on the same brochure and the following one-title of first draft 8 January 1989 was The Future of Soviet Defense Spending: Does the question make any sense? (Folder 189)
- Russian Military Expenditures, 24 April 1991. Contains material related to the brochure Russian Military Expenditures, press release "Committee Issues Analysis of Russian Military Expenditures," 24 APRIL 1991 (Folder 189)
- Current News issues (Folder 190)
- Hearings on Iran-Contra affair (Folder 190)
- Draft copies of "Has America Caught Up?-The U.S.-Soviet Military Balance," 1991, 8 October 1991 and "U.S. Foreign and Defense Policy in a Post-Soviet World," end of March 1992 (Folder 190)
- Boston University Publications (Folder 191)
- Hearings on Iran-Contra affair (Folder 191)
- Current News and Arms Control Update loose issues (Folder 192)
- Laborers International, contains material re. the lease of a suite on 16 th Street, end 1983-1992 (Folder 192)
- NRECA, contains material on the previous lease, to National Rural Electric Cooperative Association, on 1800 Mass Ave, NW (Folder 192)
- Pettit & Martin, correspondence on the end of occupation of 1800 Mass Ave (Folder 192)
- Office movers (Folder 192)
- Move: Neptune (Folder 192)
- Material on CPD Insurance (Horenberg) (Folder 192)
- Material on furniture and refurbishing (Folder 192)
- Loose articles on CPD, CPD members and other think tanks (Folder 193)
- CPD-Letter to President on START-6 1 82 (Folder 193)
- EVR-CPD INF Testimony, contains memo of conversation of meeting with George Shultz, 20 Jan 1988; draft of prepared statement for CPD testimony on INF, Feb 1988 (Folder 193)
- Loose draft copies of Arms Control and Soviet Challenge, October 1987 (Folder 194)
- The Defense Effort contains material on the preparation of this brochure; initial title was Today's Challenge and how to meet it or A Time for Renewal. (Folder 194)
- Loose material on CPD poll on Nuclear Freeze, 19 April 1984 and Application to the Smith Richardson Foundation from CPD, 27 March1984; revised questions for the Survey (Folder 194)
- More loose material on the poll on nuclear freeze; press release; letter from Iklé to the National Security Advisor on the poll (Folder 195)
- Freeze Polls (Folder 195)
- Loose material on the poll (Folder 196)
- Poll (Folder 196)
- Committee on the Present Danger, articles on CPD and CPD people (Folder 196)
- Current News Loose issues (Folder 196)
- Current News Loose issues (Folder 197)
- Current News Loose issues (Folder 197)
- Analysis of Fiscal Year 1981 CPD Defense Budget, includes material on this brochure and a press release Feb-March 1980 (Folder 197)
- A Program for Military Independence, material related to a draft, 22 Feb 1980 (Folder 199)
- Defense Strategy and Funding for the 1980s, produced by CPD 9 May 1980 (Folder 199)
- Verification Paper and Comments (Folder 199)
- SALT II, CPD Statement (Folder 199)